Sachin Dixit

Software/Web Developer

An enthusiastic developer who's keen to work and give his best to become a successful expert in the field of information technology by channelizing my technical knowledge and skills to ensure personal and professional growth and to continue to the prosperity of the organization.



sd9891317@gmail.com



9582246585



Noida, India

SKILLS

С

HTML



JAVASCRIPT

NODEJS



MySal

communication skills

time management

leadership quality

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hind

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Web application

Creating Websites

Coding

EDUCATION

B.tech in Computer ScienceITS Engineering College 70.13%(present)

2020 - Present

12TH

Vanasthali Public School 78.2%

2019 - 2020

CBSE 10th Standard

Vanasthali Public School -secured 88%

2017 - 2018

PERSONAL PROJECTS

NOU e-GYAN

- Made using html, css, java, sql
- □ https://github.com/sachin7902/NOU-e-GYAN ☑

Virtual Assistant

- Made using html, css, javascript
- □ https://github.com/sachin7902/VirtualAssistant 🗹

Covid-19 Tracker

- Made using html, css, javascript,json
- □ https://github.com/sachin7902/Covid-19-Tracker 🗹

Snake Game

- Made using html, css, javascript
- https://github.com/sachin7902/SnakeGame

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer InternBharat Intern

09/2023 - 10/2023

Tasks

- Personal Portfolio
- Netflix Home-Page Clone

Java Full Stack Training SoftPro India

08/2023 - 10/2023

PROFILES

GitHub

https://github.com/sachin7902

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sachin-dixit-6b289621a